Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Files
  - Project Files
    - Good Shepherd Community Church - Church
      - Illinois reciprocal license (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Cost estimates (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Site plan (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Estimates - preliminary studies (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Specifications - general (1 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Specifications - general (2 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - New specification sheets (1 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - New specification sheets (2 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Construction (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Gracy, David - Residence
      - Correspondece, Project No. 103 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 103 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Shadow patterns data, Project No. 103 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Specifications, Project No. 103 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Greer, Howard - Residence
      - Correspondence, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Agreements & contracts, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Bills, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Estimates, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Architect's statements, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Materials bills & vouchers, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Certificates, statements of credit & extras in full, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 128 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Greer, Howard - Residence & additions
      - Roof data & correspondence, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 33)
      - Architectural agreements, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 34)
      - Architectural certificates, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 35)
      - Estimates - roof data, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 36)
      - Cost estimates - recapitulations, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 37)
      - Engineering data, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 38)
      - General specifications, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 39)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 40)
      - Contractor's agreements & certificates, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 41)
      - Bids, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 42)
      - Construction - job notes, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 43)
      - Material bills & vounchers, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 44)
      - Notice of completion, Project No. 184 (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Greer, Howard - Dress making plant
      - General, Project No. 156 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Griffith, Raymond - Yucca Vine Market
      - General, Project No. 51 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Bids & estimates, Project No. 51 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Vouchers, Project No. 51 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Contracts, Project No. 51 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Fixtures, Project No. 51 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Specifications, Project No. 51 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Griffith, Raymond - Residence
      - Bath & library alcove, Project No. 92 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Library & bath - bills, Project No. 92 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Ranch house & garage - specifications, Project No. 92 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Bills, Project No. 92 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Architect's agreements, certificates, Project No. 92 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Copper roof, Project No. 92 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Contractor's certificates, contracts, specifications, notice of completion, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Air conditioning adjustment, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Agreement, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Maisch bills - repairs on home, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Extra orders - Martin, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Balance outstanding - Nov. 1936, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Planting specifications, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - General (1 of 2), Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - General (2 of 2), Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Farm unit, Project No. 92 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Photographs, Project No. 94 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Haight, George - Residence
      - Correspondence & miscellaneous, Project No. 107 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Landscape & excavation contracts, Project No. 107 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Bids & sub-contracts, Project No. 107 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Specifications, Project No. 107 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Contracts, Project No. 107 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Bills & receipts, Project No. 107 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Haight, George - Residence model
      - General, Project No. 116 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Halfhill, H.J. - Apartments
      - General, Project No. 72 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Handley, Alan - Residence remodel, Project No. 321
      - Construction (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Construction - sub-contractors (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Construction - notice of completion (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Owner / architect agreement (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Specifications - general (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Construction - architect / owner agreement (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Contractor's certificates (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Construction - vouchers (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Construction - contractor's correspondence (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Construction - review, 17 Nov. 1966 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Construction - list of sub-contractors (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Construction - job status, 17 Nov. 1966 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - Estimate - to complete job, 17 Nov. 1966 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Construction - hardware list (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Estimates (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Construction - miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Hanna, Phil - Residence
      - General, Project No. 75 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Hare, Robert - Residence remodel, Project No. 300
      - Supervision journal (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Contract (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Roof (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Desk folder (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Client literature (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Land survey (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Architect's agreement (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Completion files (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Vouchers (Box 74, Reel 25)
      - Notice of completion and liens (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence - Wheat (attorney) (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Statement of account (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Client - correspondence (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Architect's billings (Box 74, Folder 30)
      - Reimbursement billings (Box 74, Folder 31)
      - Estimates (Box 74, Folder 32)
      - Specifications (Box 74, Folder 33)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 74, Folder 34)
      - Air conditioning (Box 74, Folder 35)
      - Proposals (Box 74, Folder 36)
      - Bills to be paid (Box 74, Folder 37)
      - Bids (Box 74, Folder 38)
      - Bills not paid (Box 74, Folder 39)
      - Competition (Box 74, Folder 40)
      - Items to be completed (Box 74, Folder 41)
      - Stone data (Box 74, Folder 42)
      - Specifications - general (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Bar proposals (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Contractor's agreements (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Contractor certificates (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Contractor vouchers (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Contractor - correspondence (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Specification notes (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Work to complete, June 1, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Sub-contractors (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Bids (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Unpaid bills (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Planting (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Job notes (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Harris, Leonard - Residence, Project No. 305
      - Catalog (Box 75, Folder 31)
      - Client - correspondence (Box 75, Folder 32)
      - Client - notes & cuts (Box 75, Folder 33)
      - Land survey (Box 75, Folder 34)
      - Architect's agreements (Box 75, Folder 35)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 75, Folder 36)
      - Estimates (Box 75, Folder 37)
      - Specifications (Box 75, Folder 38)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Hotel, Project No. 182
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Goldman property - sub-contracts, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Pool pavillion construction - job notes, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Pool pavillion - bids, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Gallery data, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Pool pavillion - Holberg data, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Outstanding Holberg bill against main house & property, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Tennis court, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Pool pavillion - Pan Pacific Plumbing, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Pool pavillion - contractor's statements of accounts & releases, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - Pool pavillion - re final settlement, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - Roof reconstruction & waterproofing, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - Pool pavillion - lighting, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - Pool pavillion - construction contracts, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - Pool pavillion - statements of account re final settlement, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - Abe Friedman contract & data, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 25)
      - Contractor Holberg's certificates & vouchers, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - Pool pavillion - sub-contractors' certificates, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - Pool pavillion - construction correspondence, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 28)
      - Pool pavillion - Paul Wright data, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Pool pavillion - specifications, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 30)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 31)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      - Pool pavillion - architect's agreements - dressing rooms & pool lounge, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      - Pool pavillion - engineering, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 34)
      - Pool pavillion - cost estimates, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Pool pavillion - quantity surveys, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 36)
      - Pool pavillion - client correspondence - dressing rooms & lounge, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 37)
      - Carndon Park - Goldman property - correspondence, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 38)
      - Pool pavillion - client correspondence, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 39)
      - Pool pavillion - client notes & cuts, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 40)
      - Pool pavillion - land surveys, negs in Rustic Canyon, 3/3/51, Project No. 182 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square Inc. - Arena Plan, Project No. 207
      - Client - equipment & technical data, Project No. 207 (Box 54, Folder 42)
      - Client notes & documents - general data, Project No. 207 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      - Client notes, Project No. 207 (Box 54, Folder 44)
      - Photographs - billings, Project No. 207 (Box 54, Folder 45)
      - Land survey, Project No. 207 (Box 54, Folder 46)
      - Zoning, Project No. 207 (Box 54, Folder 47)
      - Quantity surveys, Project No. 207 (Box 54, Folder 48)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square, Inc., Project No. 207/208
      - Client's correspondence, Project No. 207/208 (Box 54, Folder 49)
      - Estimated gross income, Project No. 207/208 (Box 54, Folder 50)
      - Estimated square of theatre annex, Project No. 207/208 (Box 54, Folder 51)
      - Estimates, Project No. 207/208 (Box 54, Folder 52)
      - Consultant's files, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Architect's files, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Daily journal, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Job notes, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence - Bersson, William, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Estimates, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Engineering estimates, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Agreements, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Certificates, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Temporary parking, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Tower addition, Project No. 207/208 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square - Diagonal axis studies #1 & #2, Project No. 224/226
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 224/226 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square annex & parking building, Project No. 228
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 228 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Shop & parking annex model, Project No. 228 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Bersson's correspondence, Project No. 228 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Hartford Huntington - Rustic Canyon Properties, Project No. 204
      - Desk folder, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Notes & cuts, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Zoning data, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Land survey, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - Architectural agreements, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Architectural certificates, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Work orders, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - Electrical, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      - Quantity survey, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 26)
      - Estimates - engineering, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 27)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 28)
      - Specifications - writer's duplex, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 29)
      - Specifications - painter's studio duplex, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - Specifications - farm units & others, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 31)
      - Specifications - studio building, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 32)
      - Notes & holding, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 33)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 34)
      - Construction bids, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 35)
      - Construction - daily journal, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 36)
      - Construction - miscellaneous, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 37)
      - Writer's duplex, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 38)
      - Bonds, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 39)
      - Construction - contractors' agreements, Project No. 204 (Box 55, Folder 40)
      - Contractor's certificates & sub-contractors' certificates, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Contractor's certificates & Farmstead Group, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Contractor's certificates & vouchers - Palfi, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Contractor's certificates & vouchers, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Contractor's correspondence, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Writer's duplex reconstruction - contractor's certificates, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Service building - plumbing, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Sub-contractor's contracts & certificates, Project No. 204 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square, Inc. - Elevator Lobby, Project No. 223
      - Theatre model, Project No. 223 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Fine Arts Galleries, Project No. 236
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Model contract, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Construction bids, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Quantity & cost estimates, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Photographer, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Land survey - zoning data, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Outline of building requirements & purposes, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Construction supervision, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Specifications, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Architect's agreements, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Architect's final agreement, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Notes, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Attorney, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Land survey, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Original programs, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - Client's correspondence [including termination of service], Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 27)
      - Client's notes, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - Client's correspondence, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - Client's correspondence - Hardecker, Project No. 236 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Hartford, Huntington - Outpost Club
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - FLW agreements, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - FLW & LW correspondence, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Material bills & vouchers, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Outline, Project No. 181 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Headly, George W. - Residence
      - General, Project No. 142 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 142 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Agreements & certificates, Project No. 142 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Specifications, Project No. 142 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Permits & land survey, Project No. 142 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 142 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Healy, P.J. - Residence
      - Agreements, Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Certificates, Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Estimates, Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Estimates - engineering, Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - Construction - contractors (1 of 2), Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - Construction - contractors (2 of 2), Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - Client's correspondence, Project No. 196 (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - General, Project No. 196 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Sub-contractor's agreements (1 of 2), Project No. 196 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Sub-contractors' agreements (2 of 2), Project No. 196 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Bids, Project No. 196 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Construction - daily journal, Project No. 196 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Sub-contractors' certificates (1 of 2), Project No. 196 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Sub-contractors' certificates (2 of 2), Project No. 196 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Healy, P.J. - Cabinet work, Project No. 283
      - General, Project No. 283 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Healy, P.J. - Gate & barbecue remodel, Project No. 219
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 219 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Construction - sub-contractors' miscellaneous, Project No. 219 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Construction - sub-contractors' correspondence, Project No. 219 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Healy, P.J. - Potting shed, Project No. 212
      - General, Project No. 212 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Hearn, Edward - Remodel & addition & remodel, 239, 263
      - General (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Residence
      - General, Project No. 117 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Contracts & specifications, Project No. 117 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Hardware vouchers, Project No. 117 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 117 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Electrical vouchers, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Certificates, statements, & extra carbons, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - General specifications, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Bills, notice of completion, notebook, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Bids, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Bills outstanding, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous estimates, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Mats, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Changes, bills, contracts, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Florence Heifetz, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Florence Heifetz - notes & cuts, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Florence Heifetz - land surveys (maps), Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Florence Heifetz - plan checks & records, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Bills, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Work as of 1940, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, Project No. 117 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Addition & remodel, Project No. 217
      - Construction, Project No. 217 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - General, Project No. 217 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Paid bills, Project No. 217 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Construction contractor, Project No. 217 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Paid & unpaid bills, Project No. 217 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Lounge room alteration, Project No. 217 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Pool - pavillion, Project No. 217 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Beach house, Project No. 289
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Land survey, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Architect certificates, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Architect studies, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Engineering estimates, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Specifications, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Construction bids, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Supervisor's journal, Project No. 289 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Pavilion at studio, Project No. 206
      - Door data, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Land survey, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Legal data for final arbitration, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Arbitration letters, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Statement data on remodel, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Disbursement statements, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Schedules A, B, C, D & statements of costs, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Data on incinerator repairs, Project No. 206 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Construction, architect's certificates, superintendant's journal, estimates, Project No. 206 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Statement of account, Project No. 206 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - General, Project No. 206 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Pool and terrace, Project No. 279
      - Correspondence, Project No. 279 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Roof repair, Project No. 266
      - Roof data, Project No. 266 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Studio & remodel, Project No. 177
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 177 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Quantity survey, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 1)